// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Write 20/8 in mixed fraction",
    answer: "2½",
    options: [
      "2¾",
      "2½",
      "2¼",
      "2 1⁄8"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Calculate the perimeter of a triangle is (cm) whose dismensions are 1m 60cm, 1m 80cm and 2m",
    answer: "540cm",
    options: [
      "460cm",
      "540cm",
      "576cm",
      "660cm"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The point of intersection of x and y axis in a graph is called a/an",
    answer: "origin",
    options: [
      "cartesian",
      "coordinate",
      "origin",
      "plane"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "In a toss of a fair die, the probablity of getting a five is",
    answer: "1/6",
    options: [
      "1/2",
      "1/6",
      "1/5",
      "5/6"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Simplify -8(-12)+(-2)",
    answer: "+2",
    options: [
      "-22",
      "+22",
      "-2",
      "+2"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Write the sum of MC and CD in Hindu-Arabic",
    answer: "1500",
    options: [
      "1100",
      "1300",
      "1500",
      "1700"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Solve the simultaneous equations of x + y =8 and x - y =2 ",
    answer: "pre-sale service",
    options: [
      "x=3, y=5",
      "x=-3, y=-5",
      "x=5, y=-3",
      "x=5, y=3"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Factorise 3xy + 6yz",
    answer: "3y(x + 2z)",
    options: [
      "9xyz",
      "36xyz",
      "3y(xz + 2z)",
      "3y(x + 2z)"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Find the area of parallelogram with base 8cm and vetical height 5cm",
    answer: "80cm2",
    options: [
      "80cm2",
      "40cm2",
      "26cm2",
      "13cm2"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "A tennis ball is typical example of ",
    answer: "sphere",
    options: [
      "circle",
      "cone",
      "hemisphere",
      "sphere"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "if F is the number of Faces, E is the number of Edges and V is the number of Vertices, calculate V - E + F for a hexagonal prism",
    answer: "2",
    options: [
      "2",
      "4",
      "6",
      "8"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "_______ has an infinite number of lines of symmetry",
    answer: "circle",
    options: [
      "circle",
      "rectangle",
      "square",
      "equilteral triangle"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Find the meddium of the folloing decimal number 0.1, 0.2, 0.3, 0.4, 0.6, 0.7 and 0.8",
    answer: "0.4",
    options: [
      "0.1",
      "0.3",
      "0.4",
      "0.6"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "The sum of angles in a pentgon is",
    answer: "540®",
    options: [
      "360®",
      "480®",
      "540®",
      "720®"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Express 100111two in base ten",
    answer: "39ten",
    options: [
      "32ten",
      "36ten",
      "38ten",
      "39ten"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "Simplify 3 1⁄6 + 1 1⁄4 - 2 1⁄4",
    answer: "1 3⁄4",
    options: [
      "2 3⁄4",
      "2 1⁄4",
      "1 3⁄4",
      "1 1⁄4"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "A prime has only two factors which are ______ and ______",
    answer: "itself and 1",
    options: [
      "1 and any other number",
      "2 and 3",
      "1 and 2",
      "itself and 1"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "A men is x years old and his son is y year old. What is their average age?",
    answer: "(x⁄2 + y⁄2)",
    options: [
      "(½ 2XY) years",
      "(x + y) years",
      "(x⁄2 + y⁄2) ",
      "(x+y)/2xy"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "If the sum of even and prime number given even number, what is the actual value of the prime number?",
    answer: "1",
    options: [
      "7",
      "5",
      "3",
      "1"
    ]
  },



  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "_______ divides a circle into equal parts",
    answer: "diameter",
    options: [
      "arc",
      "chord",
      "diameter",
      "radius"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 21,
    question: "Simplify t [t - (1 + t)]",
    answer: "1+t",
    options: [
      "1+t",
      "t-1",
      "1-t",
      "t"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 22,
    question: "Calculate the volume of a cube of length 8m",
    answer: "512cm2",
    options: [
      "24cm2",
      "512cm2",
      "576cm2",
      "800cm2"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 23,
    question: "Find the reciprocal of 1⁄5 ",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
      "-5",
      "0.2",
      "1⁄25",
      "5"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 24,
    question: "A trader made a profit of 35% on an article he brought for N5000.00. How much did he sell the article",
    answer: "N6750.00",
    options: [
      "N1750.00",
      "N3250.00",
      "N6750.00",
      "N7500.00"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 25,
    question: "Find the difference between the media and the mode of the scores 4,3,5,9,4,6,3,8,6,4,5",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "5",
      "4",
      "3",
      "1"
    ]
  },
];